bolee.com 2018-12-16

# Free Classified in Pakistan for Mobile Phones Jobs Cars Property and More - Bolee.com

This Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in connection with www.Bolee.com (the Site). This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarized form.

## Commitment:

Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to respecting the privacy of our customers and others and handling your personal information in accordance to the most secure and safest standards. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, store and disclose your personal information.

## Collection of Personal Information:

The Site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address) and demographic information (such as address postal code and age) and other information that is used by us to provide services. We use the customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information that he or she has requested regarding the Site or regarding services offered by us. This Site uses an ad form for customers to place online and/or print ads. One of the express purposes of the Site is to gather contact information provided voluntarily by customers to be published either online or in print, as the case may be, and in connection with items that are for sale by customers. We have no control over who views online or print ads. Contact information provided may be used to contact customers when necessary. We may collect customers financial information (such as account or credit card numbers) to bill the user for products and services, but retain this information only as required to process the transaction and for as long as may be required by law.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at the Site. We use this data to tailor each visitor's experience at the Site, showing the user content that we think he or she might be interested in, and displaying the content according to the user's preferences.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (such as email addresses) and demographic information (such as postal code and age). We use contact data from our surveys to send users information about our products and services.

We may use customer information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. We also use information from customers for accounting and transaction completion purposes.

We use third-party advertising companies like Google to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information, specifically for Google, [click here to read the ad serving policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

## Disclosure of Personal Information:

We may disclose certain personal information as follows:

  * by publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers
  * to third-party websites and publishers so ads (or the content of the ads) published on Bolee can also be published on a broader array of venues or information vehicles,
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or
  * to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.
  * By having your mobile number listed on Bolee.com, you agree to receive SMS from users who may wish to contact you through the site.

Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.

## Communications and email tools:

You agree to receive marketing communications from us unless you tell us that you prefer not to receive such communications. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply indicate your preference by following directions provided with the communication. You may not use our site or communication tools to harvest addresses, send spam or otherwise breach our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. Bolee may automatically scan and manually filter messages sent via our communication tools for malicious activity or prohibited content, but Bolee does not permanently store such messages. Bolee reserves the right to delay replies in cases of suspected fraudulent activity or violations of the [Bolee Terms of Use](http://www.bolee.com/terms_of_use) and/or to refuse to transmit messages. If you use our tools to send content to a friend, Bolee doesn't permanently store your friends' addresses or use or disclose them for marketing purposes. To report spam from other users, please contact [customer support.](http://www.bolee.com/submit_ticket)

## Cookies and IP Addresses:

We may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer. A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

  * Bolee offers certain features that are available only through the use of cookies.
  * Bolee uses cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services. For more information on your choices about accepting cookies, consult your browser help function.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. Bolee does not allow these companies to collect any personal information about you using these cookies.

## Links:

This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

## Security:

We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, but as you probably know, nothing's perfect, so Bolee makes no guarantees.

## Opt-Out:

When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their information from our database, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from us. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please contact us. 

## Corrections/Contact:

Users of this Site may contact Bolee to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, and we will take necessary measure/s to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate. 

## Contact Us:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact us by going to the Contact Uspage or sending us an email directly to [info@bolee.com](mailto:%20info@bolee.com)
